{"data":[{"question":"Do not walk _____ the grass.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"2"},{"question":"Put the rubbish _____ the bin.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"2"},{"question":"Look! There's a cat _____ the roof.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"2"},{"question":"Write your name _____ the top of the page.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"2"},{"question":"Paul works _____ a school","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"2"},{"question":"There's somebody ____ the door.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"2"},{"question":"The television is ____ the living room.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"2"},{"question":"Put the notice _____ the noticeboard.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"2"},{"question":"When the weather is nice Mrs Bruckner sits ____ her balcony.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"- Use at with particular positions or places\n- Use in with a position or place, when something or someone is inside a larger thing such as a room\n- Use on with a position or place, when one thing is attached to or touching another","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"2"},{"question":"The horses are running ___ the field.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"2"}]}